<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Genthus</title>
    <link>http://genthus.art/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Genthus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 10:06:39 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://genthus.art/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Small Mess System v1.0</title>
      <link>http://genthus.art/blog/posts/small-mess-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 07:59:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://genthus.art/blog/posts/small-mess-system/</guid>
      <description>The Small Mess system (SMS) works on the idea that a small mess is inevitable when working on a creative project, be it an unorganized stack of notes, pencils scattered on a desk or a mood-board with lots of images. These small messes are not a problem when we&amp;rsquo;re working, but at some point, they start to blend into each other and turn into a huge mess, which is now intrusive to our creative process and needs to be cleaned up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Yomichan Settings</title>
      <link>http://genthus.art/blog/posts/yomichansettings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 20:43:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://genthus.art/blog/posts/yomichansettings/</guid>
      <description>Yomichan Custom CSS If you want to have your Yomichan/Yomitan look cool like mine copy the code below and add it in Configure Custom CSS -&amp;gt; Popup CSS in the settings page.
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 26 27 28 29 30 31 32 33 34 35 36 37 38 39 40 41 42 43 44 45 46 47 48 49 50 51 52 53 54 55 56 57 58 59 60 61 62 63 64 65 66 67 68 69 70 71 72 73 74 75 76 77 78 79 80 81 82 83 84 85 86 87 88 89 90 91 92 93 94 95 96 97 98 99 100 101 102 103 104 105 106 107 108 109 110 111 112 113 114 115 116 117 118 119 120 121 .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gear</title>
      <link>http://genthus.art/blog/static/gear/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 19:12:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://genthus.art/blog/static/gear/</guid>
      <description>PC Intel 12600k Cooler Master Hyper 212 Cooler Gigabyte Z690 UD DDR4 ATX LGA1700 Motherboard Corsair Vengance 32GB (2x16GB) DDR4-3600 Nvidia GTX 1080FE 8GB GPU Corsair RM650x 80+ Gold Power Supply Drawing XP-Pen Artist 24 (2k QHD version) So far this has been a really nice pen display, I think I got it for aroung 600 USD and its been well worth it. If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking of buying a pen display, I really think you should get a 2k QHD one and definitely look out for the color accuracy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software</title>
      <link>http://genthus.art/blog/static/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 19:12:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://genthus.art/blog/static/software/</guid>
      <description>General Computer Utilities OS: Windows 11 Video player: MPV Audio player: Foobar2000 Text Editor: NeoVim Browser: Firefox E-mail Client: Thunderbird Music: Spotify Torrent Client: qBitTorrent VPN: MullvadVPN Password Manager: Bitwarden Drawing Drawing program: Clip Studio Paint Pro Reference gathering: Pinterest, Pexels Reference displaying: PureRef Japanese learning Flashcards: Anki Utilities: Yomitan Textractor PowerToys Text extractor Gaming Android Emulator: LdPlayer </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website Info</title>
      <link>http://genthus.art/blog/static/websiteinfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 17:27:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://genthus.art/blog/static/websiteinfo/</guid>
      <description>I made this website after struggling to find a place in the different social media sites, with none being exactly what I wanted so here I am reinventing the wheel.
Github repo for the website Tech used in this website HUGO Tailwind 3 Github Pages </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>400 Days of Learning Japanese</title>
      <link>http://genthus.art/blog/posts/nihongo400/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 10:06:39 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://genthus.art/blog/posts/nihongo400/</guid>
      <description>It has been around 400 days since I got started on the journey to become jozu, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned a lot of Japanese, and also learned a lot about learning to learn Japanese. Stick around and maybe you&amp;rsquo;ll misinterpret my advice and come up with something that&amp;rsquo;s actually useful.
I think the moment I decided to learn Japanese might have been with the release of the Tsukihime remake, I remember telling myself that I could probably learn Japanese earlier than there would be a decent translation of it, and from there I downloaded Duolingo because &amp;ldquo;how else does one start learning a language&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
